users.skynet.be 2011-11-19

# Privacy policy

Privacy policy
Privacy policy with respect to Belgacom websites
Belgacom understands your need for online privacy and knows that privacy is also an important issue for you. That is
why we do our best to respect your privacy when you use this website.
Collection and use of personal data
Personal data is compiled at several locations on the Belgacom website. The personal data may be collected via
electronic forms which you must fill in when you order a product or service, subscribe to a newsletter, request
information or take part in a survey or competition. Data may also be compiled when you use a service that is offered
on the website.
The personal data you fill in via these channels is stored in files held by Belgacom SA under public law (Bd. du Roi
Albert II, 27, B-1030 Brussels). This data is used to provide you with the service or information that you requested, to
improve service quality and to inform you about Belgacom products, services and special offers. The compiled data can
be combined with data about your use of other Belgacom services which will allow us to tailor our offers more closely to
your needs.
This data and your identification details can also be shared with Belgacom Group subsidiaries in order to keep you
informed of products and services offered by the entire Belgacom Group.
If you do not wish to receive information about Belgacom products and services or if you object to your data being
shared with Belgacom Group subsidiaries, please read the instructions at the end of this text on how to inform us of
your wish for privacy.
You have the right to consult and, if necessary, rectify your personal data. To do so, please send a dated and signed
request, together with a copy of your ID card, to Belgacom Group Legal Services at the address given above.
If your personal data needs to be changed, we invite you to submit your change request via our website (currently only
available to customers of the Proximus services). We will amend your data as soon as possible based on your request
and the information you provide us.
Protection
The databases in which your data is stored are protected against unauthorized access.
Third parties acting on Belgacom’s behalf may be given access to Belgacom's files. Such third parties only have access
to this data on a need-to-know basis to enable them to complete their assignments for Belgacom. Otherwise the
collected data is not disclosed to third parties unless explicitly specified or the communication of your data is required
by law.
Cookies
Cookies are used on this website. A cookie is a file that is sent from the website server to your computer’s hard drive
when you consult the website. The code contained in the cookie makes it possible to identify your PC the next time you
visit the site. Cookies are used to store information which can make it easier for you to use this website: for example,
they enable your language choice to be registered, so that you are automatically routed to that language the next time
you visit the site. Cookies are also used to tailor the website to your interests or to check your use of the SMS service
on this website.
If you do not want to accept any cookies, you can reject them via your browser settings.
Cookies are also used in the e-Services section of this website to personalize use of the services and to check your
identity carefully when you ask for access to personal information. These cookies are necessary to ensure that the e-
Services function properly. If you refuse these cookies, certain parts of our website may no longer be accessible to you.
Connection data
We register information about the connection you make to our website and about the software you use to accomplish
this. This information includes your IP address, the time of your visit to the website, the type of browser you use and
the pages you visit. This data is used to create anonymous statistics and improve the quality of our website and service
through analyses of your surfing behavior on our website.
If you log in via the e-Services part of the website, we can use the data about your surfing behavior to offer you a more
personalized selection of services and products which are better tailored to your specific needs.
Online SMS
The SMS messages which you send via the e-Services ("SMS sender" on the Belgacom website and "SMS online" on the
Proximus website) are treated confidentially. Data relating to your use of the SMS service is used solely for the
provision and billing of the service itself.
Hyperlinks
This website may contain hyperlinks to websites which are not managed by Belgacom. Such hyperlinks are provided
purely for information. When consulting such websites, we recommend that you carefully read their privacy policy.
Belgacom cannot be held liable for the policy or practices of the managers of such websites.
May 2011

Privacy policy with respect to Belgacom TV
The data that you provide Belgacom via various channels and the data that Belgacom collects regarding your use of the
Belgacom TV services are incorporated into the databases owned by Belgacom (Bd. du Roi Albert II 27, 1030 Brussels).
The Belgacom TV decoder is equipped with software which registers and stores the processing carried out.
This data can be processed to:
          allow the successful execution of the contract;
          ensure the correct delivery of the Belgacom TV services;
          enable us to provide you with personalized recommendations with regard to the Belgacom TV services;
          allow customer management;
          conduct market surveys and draw up user profiles;
          detect fraud, e.g. violations of intellectual property rights;
          conduct information or promotional campaigns connected to Belgacom Group products and services, including
          by post and/or e-mail. This information can be personalized according to your use of the products and
          services offered by Belgacom.
If you do not wish to be contacted for such purposes, you can inform us of your wish for privacy via the channels
mentioned below.
If you prefer non-personalized recommendations with regard to the Belgacom TV services rather than personalized
recommendations, please inform us of your choice via the selection menu on your TV screen.
The data about your use of the Belgacom TV services is stored for 12 months.
The data that is collected can be disclosed to the partners assisting Belgacom in the delivery of Belgacom TV services or
in the event that such disclosure is necessary for the delivery of the service or if you have authorized such disclosure.
Wish for privacy with respect to the sending of information about
Belgacom products and services
          You are a Belgacom telephony (fixed line), Internet or Belgacom TV customer:
          You can call the toll-free number 0800 99 487 to inform us of your choice concerning the information about
          Belgacom products and services.
          If you have access to the e-Services on the Belgacom website, you can also inform us of your choice via: My
          profile  Be the first to know  a screen will appear in which you can select your preference.
          You can call the toll-free number 0800 99 981 if you object to your data being shared with Belgacom Group
          subsidiaries.
          You are a Belgacom mobile telephony service (Proximus) customer:
          You can call the toll-free number 6030 from your Proximus mobile phone and inform us of your wish for
          privacy. If you have access to the e-Services on the Proximus website, you can inform us of your wish for
          privacy via: My login profile Be the first to know  a screen will appear in which you can select your
          preference.
          You are not a Belgacom customer:
          You can call one of the following numbers to inform us of your wish for privacy:
          0800 55 800 for private persons, liberal professionals and SMEs;
          0800 55 200 for medium-sized and large companies and public institutions.
May 2011
